visual file read system vira
Usage: vira <option> <file>

options:

  -w or --write:
       Usage: vira <file> --write <option> <text>
       writes the following string to a file
       By setting options, you can choose whether to rewrite or continue writing

       writeoptions:
       -r:
              Rewrites the contents of the file (existing contents well be lost)

              If the fike does not exist, create a new file
      -c:
          Continue writing the contents of the file as is.

      ~~~end of write options~~~

  -s or --stdin:
          Writes the contents received from standard input into the file one by one. Cannot be deleted.
  -r or --remove:
      remove to this file.
      Usage: vira <remove file> -r
  -n or --new:
      create new file.
      Usage: vira <file> -n
  -sz or --size
      Display this file size.     Usage: vira <file> -sz
